electrictoolbox.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Electric Toolbox

### What information we collect and how

The information we collect via the Website may include.

  1. Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.
  2. Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).
  3. Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website, as is standard.
  4. Data recorded by the Website which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings, this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on you computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browsers ‘help’ facility.

### What we do with your information

Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used:

  1. To process your enquiry
  2. In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information on our website. You can unsubscribe at any time.

We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

### Cookies

ElectricToolbox.com Web sites may use session cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through the site, or to allow you to customize your preferences for interacting with the site.

At no time is your private information, whether stored in persistent cookies or elsewhere, shared with third parties who have no right to that information. If you do not wish to have session or persistent cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser.

### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

You can also opt out of some third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

### Accessibility Statement

We continually strive to ensure the pages on this Web site are accessible to individuals with disabilities in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act. If you have any difficulty viewing any page with adaptive technology, please contact the webmaster.

### User Submitted Comments

**Authority**

Every user-submitted comment on our website is moderated by an Editor. Internet users posting comments on this website should not be considered as professionals.

**Confidentiality**

We remind you that everyone can read and use your comments. You do not have the possibility to erase your own comments.

**Comments**

  * Visitors commenting on this Website must behave with respect and honesty at all times.
  * Visitors commenting on this Website are required to leave their real name or username and email address in order to submit their comment.(Your email address is never published or shared)
  * Visitors may not post any commercial/advertising comments.
  * Visitors commenting on this Website must post information which is true and correct to their knowledge. We invite you to provide resources (references, links, …) on claims when possible and relevant.
  * The Editors reserve the right to erase, without notification, any comment they would judge inappropriate.

### Other Websites

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of ElectricToolbox.com then you may contact us [HERE](https://www.electrictoolbox.com/contact/).

### Disclaimer

The information on ElectricToolbox.com is for educational and entertainment purposes only and should not be used as a substitute for a competent technical / programming advice. The information and materials provided are general in nature, and may not apply to a specific factual circumstance – details may be left out which would make the advice unsuitable in your case.

Our products and advices are provided “as is” without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied. In no event shall we be liable for any damages including, but not limited to, direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages or other losses arising out of the use of or inability to use our products and/or advices.

ElectricToolbox.com retains the right to change any of these terms, the site and its content and any products and/or services at any time without prior notice.
